I said in an interview that I haven't smashed in two years and the amount of people that seem to
find that just unconscionable is like bizarre to me. I've lived on the earth for 44 years.
I lived on this earth for 19 years before I ever had anything in my guts. Why would two years be
that deep? Furthermore, I don't know if y'all know this, but your body really is special. It is.
I know mine is. And so at a certain point, it's like, I don't want just anything up in this especial.
You feel me? Furthermore, I didn't state it like it was a problem or like it was impeding upon my
ability to achieve anything, including happiness. Nonetheless, folks was like, girl, go on and get
you some. No, it's just not a thing. So I just wanted to shout out to all the folks out there
who just decided, you know, if it ain't high quality, refined, top notchery, then I just,
I don't need it in me because I feel you.